clixshare.com 2009-11-03

# clixShare.com - PPC Advertising Network - Partnership Application

## Privacy Policy

At **_clix_ Share**.com we strive to do all we can to protect your privacy. The following statement provides a detailed explanation of the ways your information is gathered and used. We made it easy for you to access the statement from every page of our web site. **_clix_ Share**'s privacy policy is subject to change, which is why we encourage you to visit our site regularly. Please understand that we are not responsible for the contents and security practices of the web sites that we provide links to.

### How we collect and use your information

#### Collecting personal information

By collecting your information we personalize your experience with our web site and help us understand your needs. **_clix_ Share** is the sole owner of the information gathered. We will not share this information with any third parties other than in the ways described in the privacy statement. We collect personal information only from our Partners at the point of creating a Client Profile. We do not collect information from Internet users that initiate keyword searches. Consolidated information gives us an idea of the number of visitors we attract and how they navigate our site.

#### Client Registration Forms

To become a Partner with **_clix_ Share** you need to complete our online registration form, which requires users to create a unique login and password and provide contact information (name, address, web site URL). Some of the fields are mandatory and some are optional. This data will not be used or shared with third parties in any other ways except for the purpose of providing the services you requested (like submitting your website to our search engine, joining our link exchange service, sending you additional information about our company, etc.) You are not required to provide any financial information at this point in time. However, we are going to request your Social Security Number and Tax ID number after your application is approved and we start making payments to you. We also may use your contact information in cases we need to get in touch with you.

#### IP Addresses

We use IP addresses for statistical and system administration purposes. IP addresses are anonymously logged to track a user's session. We do not link IP addresses with any personally identifiable information. This means that a user's session will be logged but that users will remain anonymous to us. However, we reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a user when necessary in order to enforce our terms of service or protect our site, network, advertisers or users.

#### Cookies

**_clix_ Share** uses session cookies (small data files stored on your hard drive) to prevent banner network and affiliate system abuse and cheating. This cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information about users. Cookies are used to keep track of the client's activity on the site and make it possible for us to adjust to your preferences.

_**_clix_ Share** does not require a user to accept or use browser cookies. Most web browsers will allow you the option to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept However, the rejection of the cookie may limit your access to some areas of the Web site._

#### Sharing of Client Information

**_clix_ Share**.com does not sell, trade, rent or share customer information to other companies for any purpose.

#### Collection of Data from Internet Users

**_clix_ Share** does not collect any contact or personal information from internet users who visit **_clix_ Share**.com or any of our partner's web sites. However, we automatically collect the user computer's IP addresses and use the cookies set by the customer's browser to track the users' searching activities. This enables **_clix_ Share** to pay commissions to Clients that refer the user. We do not gather information form the user's computer to generate a unique User ID number or create "User Profiles" of any kind.

#### Links to other web sites

This website contains links to other sites. Please take into consideration that **_clix_ Share** does not take responsibility for their contents or the privacy practices. We strongly recommend our Clients to read the privacy statements of all web sites which they provide their personal or contact information to. This privacy statement only applies to information collected by **_clix_ Share**.com and through our Partners' web sites.

#### Security

  * Clients' information is protected at **_clix_ Share** in many different ways, both online and offline 
  * The data is stored behind firewalls, which are known as a very reliable security device 
  * We use the highest standards of security and confidence of holding data 
  * All the databases can be accesses only though password-protected interfaces 
  * We always us the client's information in accordance with the privacy policy statement 
  * We ask the clients' permission if we need to use their information in any way other than specified in the statement 
  * All employees are aware of our security and privacy policies and receive constant updates on them 
  * The data-storing server is secured at a carefully selected hosting facility 

#### **_clix_ Share** Privacy Policy Specifications

**_clix_ Share** will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to any third party, except for the certain situations described below: 

  * We have your express consent to share your information 
  * We need to share your information to provide you the product or service that you requested 
  * We believe in good faith that any applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it 
  * When the disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user. 

#### Notification of Changes To The Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. If at some point in the future, **_clix_ Share** changes the usage practices that affect any of your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by email of the changes. At that time you will be able to opt-out of this information usage by sending an email to **[opt-out@clixShare.com](mailto:%6f%70%74-%6f%75%74@%63%6c%69%78%53%68%61%72%65.%63%6f%6d)**

#### Choice / Opt-Out of Promotional and Marketing Communications

If you no longer wish to receive our occasional newsletters or other marketing communications from **_clix_ Share** you may opt-out of receiving these by following the unsubscribe / removal instructions located at the very bottom of these communications or by sending an email to us at **[opt-out@clixShare.com](mailto:%6f%70%74-%6f%75%74@%63%6c%69%78%53%68%61%72%65.%63%6f%6d)**

#### Updating your personal information

You can access your personal information directly by using the appropriate control panel on our Web site. We take reasonable measures to verify your identity before making corrections to your Client Profile. This is being done to protect your own privacy.

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions considering the policies indicated in the statement, feel free to contact us at: **[info@clixShare.com](mailto:%69%6e%66%6f@%63%6c%69%78%53%68%61%72%65.%63%6f%6d)**

#### Your Agreement to This Privacy Policy 

By using **_clix_ Share**.com you indicate your agreement upon the conditions of our privacy statement.
